# **Brijesh Kumar Sharma**

Email: brd1825@gmail.com

Mobile: +91 9557206286/7982889567

#### **OBJECTIVE**

To secure a challenging and rewarding position as a Software Engineer with an established organization that can utilize my skills and experience to their full potential. Having round about 1+ years of IT experience in Requirement Analysis, Design, Development and Feature Enhancement of Business/Web based applications in Web Development.

# ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

- 1. M.C.A. (Master of Computer Application) from Uttar Pradesh Technical university (Lucknow) Hi-Tech institute of Engineering and technology, U.P, Ghaziabad, 2012-2015.
- 2. B.C.A. (Bachelor of Computer Application) from M.J.P.R. university (Bareilly) Rotary institute of Management and technology, U.P., Chandausi, 2009-2012.
- 3. Intermediate Examination (U.P. Board) B.S.I. College, Aonla Uttar Pradesh 2009.
- Matriculation Examination (U.P. Board), B.S.I. College, Aonla Uttar Pradesh 2007.

### TRAINING & CERTIFICATION

- 1. Training on "Core Java" at Swarnim Infosoft Pvt. Ltd. Noida. (January 2015 to June 2015).
- 2. Training on "PHP" at Poly Infosoft Pvt. Ltd. Noida. (November 2016 to April 2017).

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**30-12-2015 To 10-03-2017:** (Under the company, FDS Ltd. Delhi).

Role: Computer Instructor/Teacher "The Union Academy Sr. Sec. School", New Delhi-01,

(Govt.-Aided Sr. Sec. School, Directorate of Education, Govt. of NCT of Delhi).

17-08-2017 To 01-12-2018: Aptara (Tech book international Pvt. Ltd.).

**Role:** Programmer/Typesetter.

**December 2018 To Present:** Astin Technology Pvt. Ltd.

Role: PHP Developer.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

**LANGUAGE** : C, C++, Core PHP, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap, Javascript, Ajax.

**FRAMEWORK**: Cake php, Codeigniter, Laravel. **OPERATING SYSTEM**: Linux, Windows XP/7/8/10,

**DATABASE** : MySQL, Oracle

1.) PROJECT ON (www.ipfcphdcci.in)		
Technologies	PHP, Codeigniter, javascript, Mysql, Apache Server	
Platform Tools:	Xampp Control Panel.	
Project Description	In the changing global scenario, the issues of IPR have gained special importance for the Micro, Small & Medium Enterprise (MSME) sector.	
Responsibilities	Programmer	

2.) PROJECT ON ( <u>www.tirhutvegunion.org</u> )		
Technologies	PHP (Laravel, HTML, css), MySql	
Platform Tools:	Xampp Control Panel.	
Project Description	This project on hold.	
Responsibilities	Programmer	

3.) PROJECT ON ( <u>www.brewadeal.com</u> )		
Technologies	PHP (Laravel, HTML, css), MySql	
Platform Tools:	Xampp Control Panel.	
Project Description	Brew A deal is an untiring effort of Lawmax Management Consultants Private Limited (LMCPL).	
Responsibilities	Programmer	

4.) PROJECT ON (https://cleanerimage.net)		
Technologies	PHP, Wordpress, Mysql, Apache Server	
Platform Tools:	Xampp Control Panel.	
Project Description	Database Development and maintenance analysis By Mysql.	
Responsibilities	Programmer	

5.) PROJECT ON ( <u>www.cars2gorentals.com</u> )		
Technologies	PHP, Codeigniter, javascript, Mysql, Apache Server	
Platform Tools:	Xampp Control Panel.	
Project Description	Cars2gorentals, general sale agent of hertz international, Dollar and Thrifty, has been operating for then 10year with a large structure focused mainly on serving the market of tourism agencies, operators and customer.	
Responsibilities	Programmer	

6.) PROJECT ON ( <u>www.astinsoftech.com/demo/funonrise</u> )		
Technologies	Opencart, javascript, Mysql, Apache Server	
Platform Tools:	Xampp Control Panel.	
Project Description	Funonrise, share the own event and famous location, Activities .	
Responsibilities	Programmer	

## **Personal Skills**

- Adaptability.
- Innovative.
- Quick Learner.
- Hardworking.

## **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Name : Brijesh Kumar Sharma

Sex : Male

Date of Birth : 18<sup>th</sup> july 1992

Marital Status : Married Nationality : Indian

Language Known : English, Hindi

Residence Address : RC-154, Archna Enclave Khoda Colony Ghaziabad, U.P.

I hereby declare that all the information provided above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place: Noida (Brijesh)